NGUYỄN HUỲNH HOÀI MY

Curriculum Vitae

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Full Name : Nguyễn Huỳnh Hoài My Date of birth : 05 December 1992

Gender : Female
Nationality : Vietnamese
Marital Status : Single

Email Address : mynguyen6512@gmail.com

Skype : ryuu_mx

Phone Number : (+84) 1262610148

Mailing Address : 23B Lê Khắc Cần, Thuận Phước, Hải Châu, TP. Đà Nẵng

PROFILE

I am an experienced software developer with extensive knowledge of programming after years of formal study and practical works. Throughout 3 years of working as a developer, I have taken part in multiple projects, working with multiple platforms and languages. Aside from software development skills, I also have plenty of experiences working with customers (using English), composing design documents and working with complicated business system.

I am a bright, ambitious and self-motivated employee who possesses sharp skills of rational issue resolving. I am also diligent, eager to learn new things and work well in group.

I am looking for a developer position where I could practice my skills as well as gain more experiences and knowledge in information technology sector. I also hope to work in a flexible, motivational and proactive work environment.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

FPT Software - FSU1.BU5

Đà Nẵng Industrial Zone, An Đồn, Sơn Trà, Đà Nẵng, VN

Developer & Junior Solution Architect August 2015 – current

- Pre-sale support and bidding.
- Analyze technical requirements to propose solutions for new projects.
- Develop & maintain web applications and web services.

Ramquest Inc

5801 Tennyson Pkwy, Plano, TX, 75024, USA

Developer (body-shopping) September 2014 – August 2015

- Work as a team member in RamQuest Closing Market team and in close liaison with external customers from US Title Companies.
- Maintain an existing software system including website, web service and portal.
- Analyze requirements and develop enhancement of the system.
- Also work with external service APIs.

FPT Software - FSU1.BU5

Đà Nẵng Industrial Zone, An Đồn, Sơn Trà, Đà Nẵng, VN

Developer & Business Analyst

December 2013 - September 2015

- Develop web applications and web services.
- Create mock-up, prototypes.
- Analyze business requirements.
- Major projects: Pavaso Digital Closing, Agency DataBase, Closing Disclosure Form.

Brando Agency

K99/11 Núi Thành, Hòa Thuận Đông, Hải Châu, Đà Nẵng, VN

Developer

May 2012 - June 2013

- Co-founder of OhYeap group precursor of Brando Company (product: OhYeap Location Social Network http://ohyeap.com)
- Contribute to designing software architect and designing database.
- Develop core features of system.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

- Diploma in Software Engineering FPT University 2014
- Best performing student of FPT University Da Nang K6B (GPA 8.67/10)
- Best performing student of FPT University Semester Spring 2012

- English : IELTS 7.5

- Japanese : N4 certification

KEY SKILLS AND COMPETENT

- Knowledge of:
 - Non-relational database and relational database design
 - OOP and SOP
 - SOAP and REST RESTful
 - Web API design and implementation
 - Android application development & PhoneGap application development
 - Unit testing
 - Amazon Web Service
- Programming skills:
 - o javascript Node.JS, Angular.JS, KnockOut.JS, jQuery
 - o C# ASP.NET Webforms; ASP.NET MVC3, 4, 5; Web API 1, 2
 - Java Spring MVC; Struts 1, 2
 - o PHP Yii framework
- Database
 - MS SQL Server, MySQL, Oracle
 - o MongoDB
- Experience of:
 - o HTML5 & CSS3
 - UML diagrams
 - XSLT, XML and JSON

- o SRS and ADD composing
- o GitHub platform, SVN, VSS, TFS
- Fluency in English communication as well as documentation.
- Ability to respond to pressure and meet tight deadlines.

PERSONAL INTERESTS

- Sports swimming, badminton
- Singing, dancing
- Reading

REFERENCES

Available on request.